Guide to the United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia Records - Addendum C
Yale University Divinity School Library
- China Files, Series IV
  - Universal Serials and Book Exchange, Washington DC (Box 37, Folder 1293)
  - University publications - miscellaneous (Box 37, Folder 1294)
  - University of East Asia, Macao (Box 37, Folder 1295)
  - University of Hawaii: Program for Chinese Journalists, 1984-1987 (Box 37, Folder 1296)
  - University of Massachusetts / Shaanxi (Box 37, Folder 1297)
  - Universtiy of Michigan (Box 37, Folder 1298-1299)
  - University of Toronto: Program, 1979-1987 (Box 37, Folder 1300)
  - Va - Ve (Box 37, Folder 1301)
  - Vi - Vo (Box 37, Folder 1302)
  - Volunteers in Asia, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 1303)
  - Wa (Box 37, Folder 1304)
  - Wan, Ai-lin, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 1305)
  - Wang: A-Z (Box 37, Folder 1306)
  - Wang, Dong-ming, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 1307)
  - Wang, Guo-ming (Box 37, Folder 1308)
  - Wang, Jian-sheng, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 1309)
  - Wang, Jian-zhong, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 1310)
  - Wang, Yao-liang, 1981-1985 (Box 37, Folder 1311)
  - We (Box 37, Folder 1311)
  - Wh (Box 37, Folder 1312)
  - Wi (Box 37, Folder 1313)
  - Williams College (Box 37, Folder 1314)
  - Wo (Box 37, Folder 1315)
  - Wr -Wu (Box 37, Folder 1316)
  - Wu: A-M (Box 37, Folder 1317)
  - Wu: Bei-ling; Studying @ SUNY, Stony Brook (Box 37, Folder 1318)
  - Wu: N-Z (Box 37, Folder 1319)
  - Wu, Zuo-ren (Box 37, Folder 1320)
  - Xi (Box 37, Folder 1321)
  - Xiamen University (Box 37, Folder 1322)
  - Xinjiang University (Box 38, Folder 1323)
  - Xu (Box 38, Folder 1324)
  - Xue, Bi-chuen (Charles) (Box 38, Folder 1325)
  - Yale-China Association (Box 38, Folder 1326)
  - Yanbian Medical College (Box 38, Folder 1327)
  - Yanbian University (Box 38, Folder 1328)
  - Ya - Yi (Box 38, Folder 1329)
  - Yang: A-Z (Box 38, Folder 1330)
  - Yang, Chuan-wei (Box 38, Folder 1331)
  - Yang, Hai ping (Box 38, Folder 1332)
  - Yang, Hsin-pao (Box 38, Folder 1333)
  - Yang, Zhi (Box 38, Folder 1334)
  - Ye Yang, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 1335)
  - Yeh, Tsung, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 1336)
  - Ying, Li-hua, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 1337)
  - Yo - Yz (Box 38, Folder 1338)
  - Yu, Timothy (Box 38, Folder 1339)
  - Yue Mei-yun (Box 38, Folder 1340)
  - Yunnan Teachers University (Box 38, Folder 1341)
  - Zhang B-Y (Box 38, Folder 1342)
  - Zhang Z - Zhao (Box 38, Folder 1343)
  - Zhang, Xin-wei (Box 38, Folder 1344)
  - Zhang, Ya-jie (Box 38, Folder 1345)
  - Zhang, Yu, 1981-1982 (Box 38, Folder 1346)
  - Zhang Zheng-sheng, 1981-1982 (Box 38, Folder 1347)
  - Zhao, Junglun (Box 38, Folder 1348)
  - Zhe - Zhu (Box 38, Folder 1349)